urbanministry.org 2006-12-30

# TechMission: TechMission - About - Privacy Policy

| 

#####   
  
home : about : **privacy policy**  

## Privacy Policy Statement for TechMission, Inc.

TechMission is firmly committed to developing community among Christian community computer centers while still protecting the privacy of our members. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

TechMission will always strive to be responsible in the management of any information obtained from anyone who contacts us. Anything less would violate the trust we keep with you, with the communities we serve, and most importantly, with God.

As with most other Internet sites, our web servers record the IP address of each visitor to this site. This IP address tells us from which domain you visited (for instance, aol.com), but not your email address or other private and personal information. We use the information we record to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer this website more effectively, and to gather broad demographic information about what countries and domains our visitors hail from and their behavior on our site.

Those who choose to register as members will be connected with a network of Christian community computer centers around the world. Contact information will be made openly available on our website as a way to encourage developing community among those involved in Christian community technology.

During the registration process, we collect a variety of demographics for active computer centers. We will not reveal individual demographics for any organization to outside groups, but we will use an aggregate of that data for grant proposals and presentations.

We use securely encrypted payment forms for all financial transactions. We obtain willingly submitted financial information in order to process payment transactions. In order to provide utmost security, we use this information only to process transactions, and do not store it in our database.

We maintain several email lists to help our members build community. We will always give our members the ability to opt-out of any mailing list.

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy without advance notice. Notice of these changes to this policy will be posted to the homepage for this website for a period of three days.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of TechMission, Inc. please contact us.

|
